17.03.2024, 19:01 My Resume



Contacts

C: +48 794 407 203
E: col.jops@gmail.com
P: http://dkupracz.cba.pl

Tech Skills

•	F HTML5	****
•	₹ CSS	****
•	Js JavaScript	****
•	⊗ React.Js	****
•	≗ Java	****
•	⊘ SpringBoot	****
•	SQL	****
•	? Python	****
•	 Flask	****

Soft Skills

- **4** Agile
- **≡** Scum
- **2**+ Teamwork
- 📵 Creativity
- Analytical thinking

Full-Stack Developer

Daniel Kupracz

I'm a big fan of new technologies and I 'm interesting about all news in the technology and IT industry. I've got immunity on stress and I can work under pressure. I quickly adapt to new jobs and quickly find myself in a new team. I try to solve problems promptly. I like meeting new people and I'm open to learning about new cultures. I want to gain a lot of experience in the IT industry and develop myself in new technologies.

"Daniel has finished the full-stack developer course and passed all exams. During the course, he learned and used frameworks and technologies such as Python, Flask, Java, Spring, SpringBoot, SQL, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and React. Daniel has a good knowledge of software design principles and relational databases. He also understands the ideas and principles behind web and web applications. Daniel can be recommended as a junior developer."

— Adam Arczyński, mentor CodecoolGlobal

Projects:

1.	• Portfolio /[HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, BootStrap]
2.	• Super Sprinter3000 /
3.	Dungeon Crawler /

Work Experience

Data Analyst nSure Insurance Agency

April 2023 - December 2023 | Poland

- Data analysis.
- Checking official government documentation
- Preparation of an insurance offer.

Logistic Worker & Teamleader Dell Logistic Center

Octomber 2019 - March 2023 | The Netherlands

- Managing the team of 49 people.
- A forklift operator.
- All werhousing works.

B2B Advisor Orange Retail S.A

May 2018 - September 2019 | Poland International

- Selling mobile phone for B2B customers.
- Creating personal offerts.
- Creating documentation for B2B customers.

Back-Office Worker Orange Polska S.A

April 2016 - April 2018 | Poland

- Managing the team of 49 people.
- A forklift operator.
- All werhousing works.

Tempolary Worker Axell Office Tilburg

17.03.2024, 19:01

My Resume

August 2015 - March 2016 | The Netherlands

- Logistic worker
- Production worker
- All werhousing works.

Tempolary Worker SBA Office Tilburg

May 2017 - June 2017 | The Netherlands

- Logistic worker
- Production worker
- All werhousing works.

Tempolary Worker Eurotemp Office Zwolle

March 2017 - May 2017 | The Netherlands

- Logistic worker
- Production worker

Profesonal Soldier Military Base Koszalin

December 2010 - January 2015 | Poland

• Military Service

Education

CodeCool

Full Stack Developer

March 2022 - June 2023

III High School

Secondary education

September 1995 - June 1999